Hello, hello friends, hello,
welcome to today's video.
In this video, we will tell you how you can
download ICICI Lombard's policy for free. If you buy ₹500 for 3 years this year, then
you can download it
from your mobile phone in a minute. What will you have to do for that?
First of all, you will know
your policy number and secondly, I will
tell you on OLX when the policy number starting from P4 has been
confirmed. It is very important to know these two things only through that you
can download your policy for free.
If you are facing any
kind of problem in downloading it, then our
service team will help you in getting the policy
and before that, you will get it from there. So
friends, let's start with how you
can remove your policy. First of all,
you will find a link in the description below. As
soon as we click on it, the app will open in front of you. The app will open
and you have to install the plan IAP icon and the app. If you click on
it like that, then
you will see the option of Om here.
Why is it that you will see a
claim for something and more, then you have to click on it,
oh my god issue foreigner, if you cook our body then who will
remember you, we need a bottle, it is
not like this here, whatever it is, it is my
Kurja, then you will see the option at the bottom,
click on Don't see your policy number, don't forget science, as soon as you click on it, it will
ask you what is
your policy number and the second option will also ask
what is your policy start date or antimatter,
as soon as you can do both these options, you
can put a seed on a question according to the policy number and policy start date and
click as soon as you click, then
you will reach your seat here
and you have to do your nutrition, in this
you have to keep in mind that the question number
of the fiber
policy in it is temporary,
so you will be able to get your policy from your hair
micron, from there you
can click on its army, if you also do
not want to go, if you also want to do
big work online, then you will get
5 to 10  Within a minute, the checkup was done
and its release of minimum amount will be charged from
you, so friends, you
can download it from open pores like this, if you liked the
video then definitely like, share and
subscribe and if you are
facing any kind of problem then you can contact on,
as you will get it in writing,
so thank you friends,
thank you very much for watching the video, if you liked the video then
definitely like, share and subscribe.